web2carz.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Web2Carz

## Privacy Statement Last Updated: July 24th, 2014

Web2Carz recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of our web sites and recipients of our e-mail newsletters. We created this policy with a fundamental respect for our customers' right to privacy and to guide our relationships with our customers. This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for all products and services owned by Web2Carz.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Web2Carz collects information from our website users, subscribers and other customers. In this section of our Privacy Statement, we describe the type of information we collect and how we use it to provide better services to our customers.

### Nonpublic personal information

When signing up for certain selected services (such as credit application), we collect nonpublic information which may include but not be limited to Name, Address, Monthly Income, date of birth and Social Security number.

We request your authorization to receive information from a consumer reporting agency (credit bureau). The authorization is transmitted to a participating lender in our network, who will actually request and receive your credit report.

### Communications with Us

We have features where our customers can submit information to us (such as our feedback forms). Where such submissions include requests for service, support or information, we may forward them to our agents, as needed, to best respond to the specific request. In addition, we may retain e-mails and other information sent to us for our internal administrative purposes, and to help us to serve customers better. Please note that letters to the editor and similar submissions may be made public.

You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below:

request@web2carz.com or call us at (888)603-2227. 

Web2Carz.com, LTD.   
P.O. Box 805   
Highland Park, IL 60035 

### Automatic Data Collection

Our web sites, newsletters and, from time to time, certain other products and services have features that automatically collect information from customers, to deliver content specific to customers' interests and to honor their preferences. This information assists us in creating products and services that will serve the needs of our customers.

For example, we may use "cookies," a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies benefit the user by requiring login only once, thereby saving time while on our web site. If users reject the cookies, they may be limited in the use of some areas of our web site. For example, the user may not be able to participate in sweepstakes, contests or drawings. Additionally, we may note some of the pages the user visits on our web sites and via our email newsletters through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs) and web beacons. The use of cookies, pixels and web beacons enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our sites and via our email newsletters.

In addition, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Web2Carz. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to Web2Carz and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

In the course of serving our advertisements to you, a unique third-party cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, we use web beacons, provided by our ad serving partners, to help manage our online advertising for Web2Carz products and services. These web beacons enable an ad server to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits these sites and to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web sites. The information used in this process is not personally identifiable.

We also may use an email delivery and marketing company to send emails (including newsletters) for which you have registered (or otherwise agreed to receive). Web beacons and cookies may be used in such email messages to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how customers use our web site and other products and services.

For our internal purposes, we gather date, time, browser type, navigation history and IP address of all visitors to our web sites. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally. We use this information for our internal security audit log, trend analysis and system administration, and to gather broad demographic information about our user base for aggregate use.

We may combine demographic information supplied by a customer at registration with web site usage data to provide general profiles, in aggregate non-personally identifiable form, about our customers and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. We may share this composite information with our advertisers and business affiliates to help them better understand our services.

### WITH WHOM YOUR INFORMATION IS SHARED

Access to the information we obtain about you resulting from loan application submission is restricted to only those service providers who need to know that information for the purpose of purchasing an automobile or obtaining credit. When you leave the box checked stating "Yes, I want to receive information and offers from email-web2carz.com & Web2Carz" - you explicitly authorize us to share your information with our preferred mailing partner for the purpose of 3rd party email messages from Web2Carz.

Other than as set forth above, we do not share personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our product(s)/service(s), and which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential.

We may share aggregate information, which is not personally identifiable, with others. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information.

### CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

We provide a way to correct or update your personal data: you may email [request@web2carz.com](mailto:request@web2carz.com).

### OPTING-OUT OF FURTHER COMMUNICATIONS

Web2Carz.com registrants may opt-out of receiving further communications from web2carz.com by:

(1) following "unsubscribe" instructions in any web2carz.com e-mail received by registrant, or   
(2) writing to request@web2carz.com. 

Unsubscribing from the Web2Carz.com email list does not automatically unsubscribe you from other email lists. Please read your email carefully to understand which email list you are unsubscribing from.

### SECURITY

We use reasonable precautions to protect our customers' personal information. Sensitive information that is transmitted online (such as Social Security number) is encrypted and is transmitted securely.

### LINKS

Our web sites contain links to other sites. Web2Carz is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information.

### CHILDREN

Web2Carz websites are not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age, and Web2Carz does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals.

### NOTIFICATION and CHANGES

If we change our Privacy Statement, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes.

### BANKRUPTCY CONSULTATION

If you opted-in to to be contacted by a local bankruptcy attorney for a free consultation (on our loan application form) and if you agree to these terms and conditions you are also agreeing to Total Bankruptcy's terms and conditions. <https://www.totalbankruptcy.com/terms_conditions.htm>

For questions about this Privacy Statement, contact:
